Guide to the Carl Djerassi Papers SC0348
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2016-142
  - Poster - Carl Djerassi: Science Backstage. Schloss-Aula der Universitat, Wyeth, 2002 (Box 2)
  - "On the Pill," by Watkins (annotated), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Chemistry Department information and contacts, 1994-2008 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Oxygen Symposium, Wisconsin, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Brochures and Programs, 2005-2015 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - "The Last 25 years of Carl Djerassi", 2013 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Internet 1, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Internet 2, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2017-172
  This series consists of publications from the 1970s-1980s about women's reproductive issues, specifically hormonal birth control and abortion.
  - Publications, 1970s-1980s (Box 1)